Hello everyone, I'm Minami-Natsu, the orange person in charge of Candy Tune.
I'm a very energetic person who lives life with a lot of energy and a lot of enthusiasm.
I'm a very stable person and I don't get upset about anything.
The members already call me mom, but I think I take good care of them.
I'm the eldest daughter, so I had my gravure taken only once a year on my birthday from the time of my 18th birthday until I turned 20.
It was during the year I turned 21 that I started my career as a gravure idol.
At first, I really enjoyed having my photo taken as a memento, but as I became more and more accustomed to being photographed as a model, it became more and more difficult for me to be photographed.
But as I got used to being photographed as a model, I wondered if it would be okay for me to be more active in gravure as a gravure idol.
I started to think about my activities as a gravure idol again,
But I started going to live shows. I was really into it, I mean, I started going to their live shows,
I was really into it,
At first, I went to big free events where various idols appeared,
I went to big free events with various idols and saw girls I had only seen on SNS in person, and I was amazed,
I was really enjoying it, and I made friends when I went there. I was very young at the time, and everyone was very considerate and friendly to me.
So I would basically go to the site by myself, have fun, and go home.
When I was chosen as a member, I didn't know the other members yet, so I didn't really feel like I was a part of the group.
When we all decided to meet each other, I felt that I was the only one with no experience.
But I thought it would be good if I could play a role to spice up the group.
I thought it would be good if I could play that kind of role.
Until we were given our own songs
I had been practicing covers and such before we were given our own song.
I've always had a tendency to learn Alfree since I was a nerd.
I've been doing it since I was a nerd.
I thought I could learn the dance too.
I thought I could learn the dance too, but I listened to the newly created song and choreographed it.
And then having the choreography and putting it into the song...
It was totally different from copying the choreography.
I think I had a lot of trouble with that.
I can't wait to sing and dance to the faces of the fans.
But I was asked the same thing by the producer, Misa-san, at the meeting.
I have one goal to be a group with a lot of good feelings.
Everyone has the same high level of consciousness and passion.
And they all think about their fans.
I think there is happiness that we try to bring to our fans, but there is also a sense of euphoria that comes from us.
I think there is a lot of euphoria that comes out from us, so I want people to come and see that.
I've been in the audience for a long time, but I've seen the live performance from the audience.
I've been in the audience for a long time, but just watching the show from the audience and seeing the idols on social media was really satisfying.
I've been in the audience for a long time.
I've never really wanted to be an idol because I want to support them.
So last year...
When I saw Fruit Zipper's live for the first time last year, the audience seemed to be having a great time.
I was really moved by the way he charmed the audience right from the soundtrack.
I was really moved.
When I saw that scene
I thought for the first time that I wanted to be like that, too, from the stage.
I wanted to create this kind of hot atmosphere from the stage.
That's when I realized that I wanted to join the band soon.
Candy Tune is a challenge for me.